boq.com.au 2013-09-22

# Privacy policy statement. Bank of Queensland Australia. Privacy.

**About this statement**  
Bank of Queensland is committed to respecting the privacy of your personal information. This policy statement explains how we collect, store, use and disclose customer personal information and what steps we take to comply with privacy laws.

 **Collection and use of personal information**  
We only collect personal information about you which is necessary for us to establish and administer your account, provide services to you or to comply with the law. This information includes details such as your name, contact address, birth date, account numbers and details, and financial information such as credit history. The purposes for which we will generally collect and use your information include complying with legislative and regulatory requirements, considering any application you make to us and providing services to you, performing administrative functions, conducting customer satisfaction research, telling you about our other products and services and products and services we distribute on behalf of other organisations. You may tell us at any time that you do not want us to advise you about other products and services.

 **Disclosure of personal information**  
We may also need to disclose information about you to certain organisations in connection with the establishment and administration of your accounts. The types of organisations to which we may disclose this information are our related bodies corporate, regulatory bodies and government agencies, your agents, including brokers or financial advisers, credit and debt agencies, agents, contractors and professional advisers who assist us in providing our services, your referees and guarantors, your or our insurers, and organisations that carry out functions on our behalf including mailing houses, data processors, researchers and collection agents, some of which may be located outside Australia. The information we provide to other organisations will be strictly limited to what is required to provide the service or comply with the law.

 **Accessing and correcting personal information**  
You are entitled to obtain access to the personal information we hold about you. If at any time you believe that the information we hold about you is inaccurate, incomplete or out of date, please contact us and, where appropriate, we will correct our records.

 **Security  
** We take all appropriate steps to prevent misuse, loss, unauthorised access to, and modification or disclosure of your personal information.

 **Data quality**  
We have a number of procedures which we follow to make sure that personal information we collect and use is accurate, complete and up-to-date.

 **Enquiry**  
We are happy to answer any further questions you may have about our management of your personal information. You can contact us at any of our branches. [Locate your nearest branch](http://boq.findnearest.com.au/) to visit.
